

Hello, I am a full stack developer and product manager who enjoys building products based on the latest, most powerful technologies. I love working with real-time APIs and applications utilizing node.js, and NoSQL datastores like MongoDB.

In my experience, not everyone at a company speaks everyone else's language. I aim to keep communication effective, and make sure every member of team - clients included - are able to understand each other and produce optimal solutions. I know the aspects of producing applications & product solutions from front to back. This allows me to successfully manage team members at each position along the way.

Stephen Rivas Jr.

Web & Mobile Developer Product Manager

Awards

Valedictorian Full Sail University, 2011

Advanced Achievement Full Sail University, 2011

Audience Choice Award NodeJam Entry, NodeSummit 2011

WorldVision Design Contest *Rebrand/Energize Proposal*

Course Director Awards
Full Sail University, 2009 - 2011
Mobile Device Development
Deployment of Flash Projects
Web Project Preproduction
Flex Frameworks
Applied Design Tools & Interfaces

Education

Web Design & Development Bachelor of Science Full Sail University, 2009 - 2011

Skills

favorite stack: [ec2, github, node.js, mongodb, backbone.js, express.js, stylus, ejs];

other tools: [RESTify, hapi.js, nodejitsu cloud, heroku cloud, lodash/underscore, iQuery, sass/stylus, twitter bootstrap, neo4j, couchdb, redis, php, bash];

concepts: [mvc, mvvm, rvp, module pattern, oop, prototypal inheritance, ux design];

Experience

Thuzi, LLC. *full stack developer, product manager* Tampa, FL June 2013 - current

- Developer on custom Event Activation Services Team used by Under Armour, Adidas, Honda, Acura, IndyCar, Verizon, and Purina
- Product Manager & Developer for Multi-Tenant Event Activation Platform which includes Full Stack Responsibilities in: deployment ops, server side & database architecture, front-end development, on-site product field testing & training, team workflow & process, UX design, as well as product features implementation vs. client needs assessment

Zeunic, LLC. owner; project manager, developer

Orlando, FL July 2011 - May 2013

- Project & Business Management
- Client Account Management
- Server Side Development
- Generated \$500k+ Online Client Revenue
- Achieved Over 1M combined page views

Freelance Developer *self-employed; web developer, front-end designer* Orlando, FL November 2009 - July 2011

- Consulted with clients to define project vision and goals
- Produced Solutions for multiple businesses
- · Balanced multiple projects, school, and life

inBurst Design Solutions owner; web developer, front-end designer Northern Colorado 2003 - 2006

- Collaborated with Industry Leaders Produced Solutions for multiple businesses
- Active Chamber of Commerce Member